Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES IV. Subject Files, 1928-1980
Sophia Smith Collection
Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES IV. Subject Files
1925-80
Planned Parenthood Federation of America
371a_s4
35 linear feet
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
The files in this series relate to organizations, individuals, conferences, grants, and a variety of topics of interest to PPFA. The materials include correspondence and printed material. Major subject categories include Associations and agencies (outside organizations), Conferences, Contraceptives, Foundations and Funds, Grant applications and proposals, Alan Guttmacher, and U.S. Government. This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
The files in this series relate to organizations, individuals, conferences, grants, and a variety of topics of interest to PPFA, such as contraceptives. The materials, which include correspondence and printed material, are arranged in one alphabetical sequence. Note that there are inconsistencies in the filing system; for example conference files appear under "C," but files related to the National Conference on Social Welfare are under "N". The Abortion subject files are located in a separate accession (not included here). Major subject categories include Associations and agencies (outside organizations), Conferences, Contraceptives, Foundations and Funds, Grant applications and proposals, Alan Guttmacher, and U.S. Government. Researchers are encouraged to check their topics alphabetically and to check under all pertinent headings. A box of material pertaining to Margaret Sanger follows the alphabetical files. It contains miscellaneous biographical material, publications, and correspondence.
NOTE: To view the series descriptions and contents lists, click on the series links below. Some files are quite large and may take several minutes to load, depending on your internet connection.
This collection is organized into ten series:
I. Chronological Files
II. Classified Files
Part 1
Part 2
III. Publications
IV. Subject Files
V. Affiliates
Part 1
Part 2
VI. Regions
VII. Minutes
VIII. Foreign
IX. Guttmacher
[SERIES X. Restricted]
PPFA has closed records created January 1, 1985 or later, with the exception of many published materials which are open to research. All records having to do with clinic defense and security are closed. PPFA has closed a small section of files in box 206 for fifty years. Researchers may request access to restricted materials from PPFA.
The Margaret Sanger Papers Microfilm Edition: Smith College Collection Series, edited by Esther Katz, et al., University Publications of America, 1995
Periodic additions to the collection are expected.
PPFA deposited these records in 1988. Various departments have since sent miscellaneous additions.
Best, Winfield; Guttmacher, Alan Frank, 1898-; McCormick, Katherine Dexter, 1876-1967; Rose, D. Kenneth; Sanger, Margaret, 1879-1966; Wattleton, Faye; Alan Guttmacher Institute--History; American Birth Control League--History; Abortion--Law and legislation-United States--History--Sources; Abortion services--History--Sources; Birth Control Clinical Research Bureau (New York, N.Y.)--History; Birth Control Federation of America--History; International Planned Parenthood Federation--History; Planned Parenthood Federation of America--History; Planned Parenthood-World Population (U.S.)--History; Birth control clinics--United States--History--Sources; Birth control--History--20th century--Sources; Birth control--Developing countries--History--20th century--Sources; Contraceptives--Research--History; Hygiene, Sexual--History--20th century; Human reproduction--Political aspects; Population policy--History--20th century; Reproductive health--Statistics; Sex instruction--History; Women--Health and hygiene--United States--20th century; Women's health services--United States--20th century
This Series forms part of the PPFA II Records
See also the PPFA I Records.
Related material can be found in the Margaret Sanger Papers, Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College, and at the Library of Congess.
- SERIES IV. SUBJECT FILES
  - Planned Parenthood Issues Manual: What It Is and How to Use It, circa 1978 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Samuel W. 1955-58 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Associations and Agencies
    - Abortion League, Inc., Correspondence 1976 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Abortion Rights Association of New York, Inc. 1972 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Academy of General Practice of Pharmacy 1972 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Adult Education Association of USA 1955-63 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Out-card for Academy of Psychosomatic Medicine 1962-64 (Box 104)
    - Advertising Council
      - 1963-74 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - 1975-78 (Box 104)
    - Advertising Council, General 1964-71 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - American Academy of General Practice, American Academy of Family Physicians 1955-72 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - American Academy of Pediatrics, General Correspondence 1959-65 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science 1955-72 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - American Association for Maternal and Infant Health 1957-70 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - American Association of Marriage Counselors, General 1955-62 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - American Association of Sex Educators
      - 1968-74 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - 1975-78 (Box 104)
    - American Association of University Women 1962-70 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - American Bar Association, Correspondence, General
      - 1967-74 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - 1975-78 (Box 104)
    - American Board of Pediatrics, Questionnaires 1966-1969 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China
      - ABMAC 1967-70 (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - General 1966-70 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - American Cancer Society, Correspondence 1957-72 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - American Civil Liberties Union
      - General
        - 1955-74 (Box 104, Folder 21)
        - 1975-79 (Box 104)
      - Minutes 1977 (Box 104, Folder 22)
      - Report on Abortion Rights Restrictions, Oct., 1978 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists 1958-65 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - American Eugenics Society 1956-66 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - AFL-CIO Community Services, Correspondence 1957-69 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - American Friends Service Committee
      - Correspondence 1961-71 (Box 104, Folder 27)
      - General, etc. 1965, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - American, Groups, various dates, miscellaneous
      - 1962-74 (Box 104, Folder 29)
      - 1975-77 (Box 104)
    - American Hospital Association 1956-73 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - American Humanist Association 1956-66 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - American Jewish Congress 1958-69 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - American Public Health Association, correspondence
      - 1966-74 (Box 104, Folder 33)
      - 1975-78 (Box 104)
    - American Medical Association
      - Correspondence
        - 1967-73 (Box 104, Folder 34)
        - 1977 (Box 104)
        - 1964-66 (Box 104, Folder 35)
      - Continuing Education Program 1963-72 (Box 104, Folder 36)
      - "Handbook," 1962-64 (Box 104, Folder 37)
      - Letter October 11, 1955re: Contraceptive Practice Study, 1955-64 (Box 104, Folder 38)
      - General 1955-64 (Box 104, Folder 39)
      - Policy 1964-63 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      - Resolutions on Birth Control 1925-64 (Box 104, Folder 41)
    - American National Council for Health Education of the Public
      - Correspondence 1963-66 (Box 104, Folder 42)
      - General 1962-65 (Box 104, Folder 43)
    - American National Red Cross 1962-1969 (Box 104, Folder 44)
    - American Nurses' Association, correspondence 1964-72 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - American Orthopsychiatric Association 1961-69 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - American Osteopathic Association, correspondence 1957-68 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - American Pharmaceutical Association 1972 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - American Public Health Association
      - Committee on Pop Control 1961-67 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence 1961-66 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Annual Meeting 1979 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Annual Meeting, Houston, Texas, Oct., 1970 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - 97th Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, PA, Nov., 1969 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Southern Branch, TV Tape on Prejudice 1968 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - 93rd Annual Meeting, Chicago, IL 1965-66 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - 94th Annual Meeting, Houston, TX 1965-66 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Western Branch, Honolulu, Hawaii 1964-65 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - Southern Branch, A Mtg., Tampa, Florida 1964 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - 91st Annual Meeting, Kansas City, MO. 1963 (Box 105, Folder 15)
      - Southern Branch Conference, Biloxi, Miss. 1962-63 (Box 105, Folder 16)
      - Annual Meeting, Miami, Florida 1962 (Box 105, Folder 17)
      - Southern Branch P H Mtg., Roanoke, VA. 1961-62 (Box 105, Folder 18)
      - Detroit, Mich. P H Mtg., Nov. 1961 (Box 105, Folder 19)
      - San Francisco P H Mtg., Oct. 1960 (Box 105, Folder 20)
      - Western Branch P H Mtg., Denver, Col., May 24-26, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 21)
      - Out-Card for American Public Health Association, Professional Examination Services Folder 1962-64 (Box 105)
      - Exhibit, Atlantic City, NJ, Nov., 1956, Oct. 1959 (Box 105, Folder 22)
      - Southern Branch P H Mtg., Miami, Florida 1958-62 (Box 105, Folder 23)
      - Prejudice: Our Professional Enemy, Mrs. Naomi Gray, Dr. Schulman, circa 1969 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - American Public Welfare Association
      - Correspondence
        - 1963-71 (Box 105, Folder 25)
        - 1959-62 (Box 105, Folder 26)
      - General 1963-68 (Box 105, Folder 27)
      - Field Trips 1960, 1969-61 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, correspondence 1961-62 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers 1968, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 30)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility 1955-63 (Box 105, Folder 31)
    - American Society of Planning Officials 1960-68 (Box 105, Folder 32)
    - American Sociological Society 1955-68 (Box 105, Folder 33)
    - Americans United For Separation of Church and State 1955-69 (Box 105, Folder 34)
    - Association For the Study of Abortion, Inc. 1973 (Box 105, Folder 35)
    - Association For Voluntary Sterilization
      - Correspondence
        - 1978-79 (Box 105, Folder 36)
        - 1963-74 (Box 105, Folder 37)
        - 1975-77 (Box 105)
      - General
        - 1969-74 (Box 105, Folder 38)
        - 1976-79 (Box 105)
        - 1964-68 (Box 105, Folder 39)
      - Amalgamation with PP-WP
        - Correspondence and general 1963-64 (Box 105, Folder 40)
        - Questionnaires 1964 (Box 105, Folder 41)
    - Blue Cross (Formerly Titled Associated Hospital Service)
      - 1964-74 (Box 105, Folder 42)
      - 1977-79 (Box 105)
    - Business Council, correspondence 1970-71 (Box 105, Folder 43)
    - Campaign to Check Population Explosion, Mugging Ad, March 10, 1968 (Box 105, Folder 44)
    - Catholic Alternatives 1975-1977 (Box 105, Folder 45)
    - Catholics for a Free Choice
      - 1974 (Box 105, Folder 46)
      - 1977 (Box 105)
    - The Center for Population Activities, Final Report Seminar-Workshop, Management Problems of Family Planning Programs, Wash. D.C., Sept. 22-Oct. 31, 1975 (Box 105, Folder 47)
  - Associations and Agencies, Miscellaneous
    - Associations and Agencies, miscellaneous, correspondence 1969-72 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - B, Misc.
      - 1953-74 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - 1975-79 (Box 106)
    - Baird, William 1963-72 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Banning, Margaret Culking 1963-64 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Bar, Misc. 1959-74 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Bas, Misc.
      - 1966-74 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - 1975 (Box 106)
    - Bastedo, Mrs. Phillip, correspondence 1971 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Baum, Mrs. Morton (Miggie) 1955-65 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Center of Concern
      - 1974 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - 1975 (Box 106)
    - Child Study Association of America, correspondence 1956-69 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Child Welfare League of America
      - 1957-74 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - 1979 (Box 106)
    - Citizens Committee On Population and the American Future 1973 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Citizens' Crusade Against Poverty
      - Correspondence, general 1966 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - General 1964 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Coalition For Health Funding 1971 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Committee for Legal Abortion, correspondence 1971-72 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Committee for Progressive Legislation 1970 (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Community Council of Greater New York 1958-67 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Community Service Society 1957-69 (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - CONVO (Coalition of Voluntary Organizations) 1979 (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - CORE 1968 (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Council of Better Business Bureau, Inc. 1979 (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Council of National Organizations
      - Correspondence 1961-63 (Box 106, Folder 23)
      - "World of Ideas," 1958, undated (Box 106, Folder 24)
      - List, meetings, general 1961-63 (Box 106, Folder 25)
      - "Project-Tomorrow," general 1959-63 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Council of Foreign Relations 1959-63 (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Council of Population and Environment (COPE) 1971-72 (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Council on Social Work, Education 1962-71 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Euthanasia Society of America 1955-65 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Family Planning Services or Guidance Agencies (List by States) 1971 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Family Service Association of America
      - Correspondence 1956-69 (Box 106, Folder 32)
      - General 1956-64, undated (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - Foreign Policy Association, correspondence 1956-68 (Box 106, Folder 34)
    - Hope, Project, correspondence 1961-69 (Box 106, Folder 35)
    - Institute of Life Insurance 1955-61 (Box 106, Folder 36)
    - Interagency Committees on Family Planning
      - General 1967-72 (Box 106, Folder 37)
      - Mimeos, general 1967-68 (Box 106, Folder 38)
    - International Childbirth Education Association 1970 (Box 106, Folder 39)
    - International Family Planning Association 1978 (Box 106, Folder 40)
    - International Independence Institute, correspondence 1965-68 (Box 106, Folder 41)
    - International Union for Child Welfare 1956-60 (Box 106, Folder 42)
    - Human Betterment Association, HBAA News and General 1955, 1964-65 (Box 106, Folder 43)
    - Joint Commission on Mental Health of Children, correspondence 1967-68 (Box 106, Folder 44)
    - The Legal Aid Society 1978 (Box 106, Folder 45)
    - League of Women Voters of the U.S. 1963-70 (Box 106, Folder 46)
    - Maternity Center Association 1956-69 (Box 106, Folder 47)
    - Medical Committee for Human Rights 1964-69 (Box 106, Folder 48)
    - Medical and Pharmaceutical Information Bureau, correspondence 1961-67 (Box 106, Folder 49)
    - Medico-CARE
      - Correspondence 1966-69 (Box 106, Folder 50)
      - Misc. and Meetings, etc. 1958, 1966-69 (Box 106, Folder 51)
  - Be, Misc. 1966-69 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Ber, Misc. 1963-69 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Bi, Misc.
    - 1955-74 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - 1978 (Box 107)
  - Birth Control
    - Birth Control Law Manuscript (New Publication) 1957, 1960-65 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Law Summary (New publication), correspondence 1957-69 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Legal Status 1963-64 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Advertising Suggestions 1960-64 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - "Complete Book of B C," 1961-68 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - "Complete Book of," for the Blind 1962-65 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Bl, Misc.
    - 1961-74 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - 1975-79 (Box 107)
  - Black Attitudes
    - 1962-74 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - 1975-77 (Box 107)
  - Blind Program 1964-67 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Bo, Misc.
    - 1961-74 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - 1975-77 (Box 107)
  - Br 1964-1969 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Bridges, Leon, correspondence 1970 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Brodeur, David A., correspondence 1964-67 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Bre, Misc. 1953-66 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Bro, Misc. 1962-69 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Bromley, Dorothy Dunbar 1958-65 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Brown, Dr. Harrison 1956-60 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Browne, Jane C., correspondence 1969-70 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Bu, Misc. 1958-69 (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - C, Misc.
    - 1964-74 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - 1975-79 (Box 107)
  - Cadbury, Mr. and Mrs. George 1960-70 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Campaign to Check Population Explosion 1968-69 (Box 107, Folder 25)
  - Campbell, Mrs. Walter E. (Loraine)
    - 1961-68 (Box 107, Folder 26)
    - Mimeo, letters, general 1956-61 (Box 107, Folder 27)
  - Canfield, Cass
    - 1964-73 (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence 1961-64 (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - "Discussion Group," 1960-62 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Dallas Rotary Club, correspondence, Dec. 1 and 2, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 31)
    - Telegrams, Poll (to Eminent Catholics) 1960-62 (Box 107, Folder 32)
  - Car, Misc. 1964-74 (Box 107, Folder 33)
  - Cayo, Felix 1961-68 (Box 107, Folder 34)
  - Ce, Misc. 1960-69 (Box 107, Folder 35)
  - Ch, Misc. 1964-69 (Box 107, Folder 36)
  - Chain, Hu 1955, 1959-69 (Box 107, Folder 37)
  - Chandrasekhar, Dr. S.
    - 1955-69 (Box 107, Folder 38)
    - 1955 (Box 107, Folder 39)
  - Chase, Ilka (Mrs. N. Brown) 1959 (Box 107, Folder 40)
  - Chase, Rowell W. 1955-63 (Box 107, Folder 41)
  - Child Abuse, Legal (Paul, Eve) 1979 (Box 107, Folder 42)
  - Childcraft, Field Enterprises Educational Corp. 1962-64 (Box 107, Folder 43)
  - Ci, Misc.
    - 1963-74 (Box 107, Folder 44)
    - 1975-79 (Box 107)
  - Citizens for P Parenthood, correspondence 1961 (Box 107, Folder 45)
  - Cl, Misc. 1960-69 (Box 107, Folder 46)
  - Closing the Gap
    - General correspondence 1966-69 (Box 107, Folder 47)
    - Infant Mortality 1967 (Box 107, Folder 48)
  - Co, Misc.
    - 1957-74 (Box 107, Folder 49)
    - 1975-79 (Box 107)
  - Comstock Laws
    - 1968-74 (Box 107, Folder 50)
    - 1975-78 (Box 107)
  - Com-n, Misc.
    - 1963-74 (Box 107, Folder 51)
    - 1975-76 (Box 107)
  - Concordia Publishing House 1958-60 (Box 107, Folder 52)
  - Consumers Union, Whitehill, Mrs. Jean L. 1957-67 (Box 107, Folder 53)
  - Conferences
    - Abortion Providers' Seminar, "The Impact of Abortion," Dallas, Texas, April 20-21, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Abortion Rights Strategy Conference, Washington, D.C., May 10, 1977 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - American Assembly
      - Arden House Conference 1963-68 (Box 108, Folder 3)
      - General 1963 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - AMA Congress on Environmental Health, General, Washington, D.C. 1969-70 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - American Medical Association
      - Quality of Life Congress, March 7-9, 1973Chicago, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Third National Voluntary Health Conference, Washington, D.C. 1969-70 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - American Public Health Association, Convention, Nov. 4-10, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Arden House Conference 1955-62 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Asian Population Conference 1963 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Aspen Conference
      - Correspondence 1962-65 (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Report 1965 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, general 1965 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Colloquy '76, Update and Challenge Discussion Conference, Princeton Campus, October 25-26, 1976 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Committee on World Food Crisis, correspondence 1968 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Conference for Legal Abortion Services In Georgia, November 4-5, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Conference on Abortion, Techniques and Services 1971-73 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Conference on Abortion, Techniques and Services, Proposed Contract Between Excerpta Medica and the Committee 1971 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Conferences on Teenagers and Family Planning 1977-78 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Denver Strategy Conference, report and correspondence, Denver, CO, Oct. 7-9, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Conference on Educational Need of College Women for Marriage and Family Planning, Gould House 1962 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Congressional Breakfast, National Academy of Sciences Report, May 25, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - First National Congress on Optimum Population and Environment 1969-70 (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - "Future of Man," Seagram and Sons, September, 1959-60 (Box 108, Folder 24)
    - Groves Conference on Marriage
      - General 1964-66 (Box 108, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence 1955-63 (Box 108, Folder 26)
      - Field Trips 1955-62 (Box 108, Folder 27)
      - General 1958-65 (Box 108, Folder 28)
    - International Conference on the Family 1960 (Box 108, Folder 29)
    - International Conference on Social Work Education, Population and Family Planning, Hawaii 1969-70 (Box 108, Folder 30)
    - International Council on Social Welfare, correspondence 1960-66 (Box 108, Folder 31)
    - International Conference on VD, Family Planning and Human Sexuality, Hawaii, June 11-18, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 32)
    - International Industrial Conference, NIBC and Stanford Research Institute, San Francisco, CA 1965 (Box 108, Folder 33)
    - International Youth Conference, Washington, D.C., February 28-March 3, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 34)
    - International Youth Conference on the Human Environment, McMaster University, Ontario 1971 (Box 108, Folder 35)
    - Macy Conference on Population and Family Planning and Medical Education, Williamsburg, VA, 11/1-3/70 (Box 108, Folder 36)
    - Migrant Conference, Correspondence 1960-62 (Box 108, Folder 37)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews 1956-62 (Box 108, Folder 38)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, Literature 1962 (Box 108, Folder 39)
    - National Conference of Friends on Race Relations, June 18-21, 1965 (Box 108, Folder 40)
    - National Conference on Abortion 1969-70 (Box 108, Folder 41)
    - National Conference on Abortion, Techniques and Services 1973 (Box 108, Folder 42)
    - National Conference on Citizenship 1955-56 (Box 108, Folder 43)
    - National Conference on Family Planning: Partners for Progress, Washington, D.C., May 5-6, 1966 (Box 108, Folder 44)
    - National Conference on International Economic and Social Development 1956-62 (Box 108, Folder 45)
    - National Conference on Planning and Providing Abortion Services, Pittsburgh, PA, Feb. 28-March 1, 1974, 1973-74 (Box 108, Folder 46)
    - National Conference on Sterilization Abuse, Washington, D.C., Sept. 23-24, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - National Industrial Conference Board
      - "Population and Growth," conference, NYC 1965-66 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence 1965-69 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - National Urban League Regional Forum Project Conference, Atlanta, May 6-8, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - National Women's Conference, Houston, Texas, Nov. 18-21, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Negro Conference, Physicians, Correspondence 1968-69 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - OEO Regional Family Planning Conference, Washington, D.C., April, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development, First Population Conference, Paris 1968-69 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Ortho Conference, Population Growth and Policy in US, Buck Hills, PA, Sept. 5-7, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Pacific Coast Fertility Society, 9th Annual Meeting, November 9-12, 1961 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Physiological Conference, Invitations, West Point, New York, July 1959-63 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Population Council
      - Conference on IUCD, New York City, April 30-May 1, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - Conference on Population Policy, 3/6-7/70 (Box 109, Folder 13)